I recently went on my first trip
without my family at the age of 17 and this
is what it taught me.  First Not Everything
Goes According to the Plan and it's
[music] okay.  Like we had a whole itery
plan but so many things never even
[music] happened.  And some how, despite all these things,
our trip was quite good.
Second is overpacking.  Like I packed so many
outfits for every possible occasion, but
the thing is, half of them didn't even make it out of my suitcase.
Third, sometimes
[music] a sunset is better than spending
your time at an aesthetic cafe.  Because that
evening reminded me not every moment
needs to be rushed.  [Music] Sometimes it's
okay to pause and simply enjoy where you are.
And lastly, the best memories don't need to be
fancy.  Like, we had places to
save every morning for our breakfast.
But we ended up cooking Rams at R BnB.
Looking back to those simple breakfasts are one
of my favourite memories from the trip.  Two I thought I would come back
with just photos and
videos but I came back with memories, little
stories and so much confidence.